Guide to the New York University Portrait Files MC.319
New York University Archives
- S
  - Silver, Julius, 1963-1965, 1979, 1988, circa 1990s (Box 100, Folder 19, Box 123, Folder 33)
  - Silver, Julius -- Portrait by John Howard Sanden, 2004; UA_MC_319_ER_2
  - Silverman, Alex, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - Silverman, Henry R., undated (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Silverman, Herbert R., 1961, 1971-1972, 1976, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Silverman, Hirsch L., undated (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - Silverman, Kenneth, 1976, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Silverman, Pauline S., 1980 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - Silverman, Saul S., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - Silverman, Sydney I., 1960, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - Silverstein, Larry, 1952-1999 (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - Simha, Robert, undated (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - Simmons, Adele Smith, undated (Box 100, Folder 30)
  - Simmons, John, 1943 (Box 100, Folder 31)
  - Simmons, William R., 1964 (Box 100, Folder 32)
  - Simon, Elena Pinto, undated (Box 100, Folder 33)
  - Simon, Gary, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 34)
  - Simon, Neil, undated (Box 100, Folder 35)
  - Simon, Paul, undated (Box 100, Folder 36)
  - Simon, William, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 37)
  - Simpson, Laurence P., undated (Box 100, Folder 38)
  - Simpson, Malcolm, undated (Box 100, Folder 39)
  - Simpson, Peter L., undated (Box 100, Folder 40)
  - Sinatra, Frank, undated (Box 100, Folder 41)
  - Sinclair, Prior, undated (Box 100, Folder 42)
  - Singer, undated (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis, 1979-1983 (Box 100, Folder 43)
  - Singer, Lloyd I., undated (Box 100, Folder 44)
  - Singstad, Ole, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 45)
  - Sinkovic, Boris, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 46)
  - Sipes, Larry, undated (Box 100, Folder 47)
  - Siris, Irwin, undated (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Sirlin, Alberto, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Sirota, Bob, undated
    - Photographs (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Sivak, Joseph, circa 1934-1935 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Sivakumaran, Sandesh, undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Skinner, Charles E., undated (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Skinner, Elliot P., 1960 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Skipitares, Theodora, undated (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Skolnick, Jerome, undated (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Skudin, Clifford, undated (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Skye, Harriet, undated (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Slain, John, 1983, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Slater, David S., 1982, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Slaughter, Anne-Marie, undated (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Slavson, Samuel R., undated (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Sleeper, Marvin, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Sliver, Henry M., undated (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Sliwa, Curtis, undated (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Sloan, Bevin, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Slobad, Elaine, undated (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - Small, Neva, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - Small, Stephen, undated (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - Smelstor, Leon, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - Smigel, Erwin D., 1962, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - Smith, A.A., undated (Box 101, Folder 25)
  - Smith, Anna Deavere, 1992, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 26)
  - Smith, Barbara, undated (Box 101, Folder 27)
  - Smith, C.E., undated (Box 101, Folder 28)
  - Smith, Carleton Sprague, 1959 (Box 101, Folder 29)
  - Smith, Carol Cordes, undated (Box 101, Folder 30)
  - Smith, Dennis, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 31)
  - Smith, E., undated (Box 101, Folder 32)
  - Smith, Edgar, 1972 (Box 101, Folder 33)
  - Smith, Edward, undated (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Edward C., 1951-1953 (Box 101, Folder 34)
  - Smith, Evelyn C., 1982 (Box 101, Folder 35)
  - Smith, Frances, undated (Box 101, Folder 36)
  - Smith, Grace, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 37)
  - Smith, H. Alvin, 1966 (Box 101, Folder 38)
  - Smith, Herbert P., undated (Box 101, Folder 39)
  - Smith, J. Augustine, undated (Box 101, Folder 40)
  - Smith, Joshua, undated (Box 101, Folder 41)
  - Smith, Nila Benton, undated (Box 101, Folder 42)
  - Smith, Oliver, 1972, 1981, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 43)
  - Smith, Paul E., undated (Box 101, Folder 44)
  - Smith, Rhoten A., 1958, 1960 (Box 101, Folder 45)
  - Smith, R.R.R., undated (Box 101, Folder 46)
  - Smith, Rufus D., 1932, 1945, 1951 (Box 101, Folder 47)
  - Smith, Russell F.W., 1964, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 48)
  - Smith, Terry, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 49)
  - Smoke, Paul, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 50)
  - Smoot, Patricia A., 1985 (Box 101, Folder 51)
  - Smulian, Don, 1996 (Box 101, Folder 52)
  - Smyth, Craig Hugh, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 53)
  - Smythe, Craig, undated (Box 101, Folder 54)
  - Sniffen, D. Austin, 1937-1939 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Snoeyenbos, Ann, undated (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Snow, C.P., 1969, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Snow, Charles Henry, 1903, 1921 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Snow, John B., undated (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Snowden, undated (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Snyder, John I., undated (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Snyder, Tom, undated (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Sobel, Morton, undated (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Sobelman, Marilyn, undated (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Sockman, Ralph W., 1961, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Sofaer, Abraham D., undated (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Soffer, Joe, 1983
    - Photographs (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Sofrarios, undated (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Sohn, Myoung-Soon, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Sokolowski, Thomas, 1984-1985 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Sokurov, Alexsandra, 1989 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - Solari, Dawn, 1981-1982 (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - Solazzo, Dan, undated (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - Soldwedel, Better J., 1963, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 20)
  - Solinger, Janet, 1966 (Box 102, Folder 21)
  - Solnet, Bernard, 1957-1958 (Box 102, Folder 22)
  - Solomon, Michael, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 23)
  - Solomon, Steve, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 24)
  - Solomon, William R., 1992 (Box 102, Folder 25)
  - Solorsky, Max, 1965 (Box 102, Folder 26)
  - Solow, Sheldon H., 1992 (Box 102, Folder 27)
  - Solwen, Burt, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 28)
  - Somervell, Brehon B., 1943 (Box 102, Folder 29)
  - Somerwille, Randolph, undated (Box 102, Folder 30)
  - Somit, Albert, 1958 (Box 102, Folder 31)
  - Somma, Salvatore, undated (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - Sommer, Frank H., 1916-1959 (Box 102, Folder 32)
  - Sonberg, Steven, undated (Box 102, Folder 33)
  - Sondheim, Stephen, undated (Box 102, Folder 34)
  - Sondhi, Puja, undated (Box 102, Folder 35)
  - Song, Bing, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 36)
  - Song, Sang-Hyun, undated (Box 102, Folder 37)
  - Sonnenreich, Joe, undated (Box 102, Folder 38)
  - Sonntag, Otto, undated (Box 102, Folder 39)
  - Sonoda, Koji, undated (Box 102, Folder 40)
  - Sontag, undated (Box 102, Folder 41)
  - Sontag, Susan, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 42)
  - Sorrin, Sydney, undated (Box 102, Folder 43)
  - Sorter, George, 1980-2000
    - Photographs (Box 102, Folder 44)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Soscie, Marie A., 1964 (Box 102, Folder 45)
  - Sosna, Morton, circa 1936 (Box 102, Folder 46)
  - Soucek, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 47)
  - South, Helen, undated (Box 102, Folder 48)
  - Souza, John Philip, undated (Box 102, Folder 49)
  - Sovern, Michael, undated (Box 102, Folder 50)
  - Soyinka, Wole, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 51)
  - Spahr, Walter, undated (Box 102, Folder 52)
  - Spagnola, Joseph, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 53)
  - Spanar, Ray, 1985-1986 (Box 102, Folder 54)
  - Spark, Bertel, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 55)
  - Sparrow, Roy, 1982
    - Photographs (Box 102, Folder 56)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 22)
  - Spaulding, Asa T., 1964 (Box 102, Folder 57)
  - Spaulding, Roland, undated (Box 102, Folder 58)
  - Spectar, Andrew, 1966 (Box 102, Folder 59)
  - Speer, Robert K., undated (Box 102, Folder 60)
  - Speigel, C.D., 1966 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Speiser, Mortimer D., undated (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Spellman, Christina, undated (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Spellman, Cardinal Francis, undated (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Spencer, Frank C., 1965-1979 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Spencer, Kathryn C., undated (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Spencer, William A., 1952 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Spencer, William C., 1959 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Sperling, George, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Spero, Sterling D., 1959 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Speyer, Dorthea, undated (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Spiegel, Roy, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Spielman, Andrew, undated (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Spinelli, Vince, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Spitz, George, 1934 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Spletzer, Paul, 1964 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Spock, Leslie E., 1964 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - Sprague, C. Hayes, 1942 (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Sprenkle, Laura, undated (Box 122, Folder 23)
  - Sprigg, Louis R., undated (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - Spring, Gardiner, undated (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - Sproul, Allan, 1947, 1963 (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - Spruch, Larry, 1967 (Box 103, Folder 22)
  - Stack, Herbert, 1938, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - Stafford, Ronald, undated (Box 103, Folder 24)
  - Stafford, Walter, undated (Box 103, Folder 25)
  - Stahl, Sigmund, 1964 (Box 103, Folder 26)
  - Stahl, William H., 1952 (Box 103, Folder 27)
  - Stam, Oliver, undated (Box 103, Folder 28)
  - Standen, Edith, undated (Box 103, Folder 29)
  - Stanford, Dr, Henry K., 1968 (Box 103, Folder 30)
  - Stanford, William, undated (Box 103, Folder 31)
  - Stangerm Abraham, circa 1958 (Box 103, Folder 32)
  - Stanley, Thomas, undated (Box 103, Folder 33)
  - Stanleyetta, Nelle, 1893 (Box 103, Folder 34)
  - Stanton, Betty, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 43)
  - Staples, Donald E., 1974 (Box 103, Folder 35)
  - Stapleton, Maureen, undated (Box 103, Folder 36)
  - Starbuck, William H., undated
    - Photographs (Box 103, Folder 37)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 24)
  - Starkie, Walter, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 38)
  - Starkman, Milton, undated (Box 103, Folder 39)
  - Starkweather, Louis, undated (Box 103, Folder 40)
  - Starr, Kenneth, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 41)
  - Starr, Wimarth H., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 42)
  - Staubli, Ursula, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 44)
  - Stead, A.J., 1906 (Box 103, Folder 45)
  - Steadman, M.C., undated (Box 103, Folder 46)
  - Stearns, Henry S., 1902-1903 (Box 103, Folder 47)
  - Stecich, Marianne, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 48)
  - Stedman, Harvey J., 1982, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 49)
  - Steele, Dr. John M., undated (Box 103, Folder 50)
  - Stefkovich, Steve, 1970 (Box 103, Folder 51)
  - Stehlin, Stewart A., undated (Box 103, Folder 52)
  - Stein, Andrew, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 53)
  - Stein, Bruno, 1974
    - Photographs (Box 103, Folder 54)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 25)
  - Stein, Emanuel, 1960-1985 (Box 103, Folder 55)
  - Stein, Meyer L., 1965-1972 (Box 103, Folder 56)
  - Stein, Dr. Morris I., 1961, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 57)
  - Stein, Rose Lehman, undated (Box 103, Folder 58)
  - Steinberg, Joseph S., undated (Box 103, Folder 59)
  - Steinem, Gloria, 1970-1980 (Box 103, Folder 60)
  - Steines, John, undated
    - Photographs (Box 103, Folder 61)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 26)
  - Steinhardt, Michael H., 2000 (Box 103, Folder 62)
  - Steitz, A., 1935 (Box 103, Folder 63)
  - Stelmach, Michael, circa 1934 (Box 103, Folder 64)
  - Stember, Karen, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 65)
  - Stempel, Enest E., 1998 (Box 103, Folder 66)
  - Sterling, A. Mary, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 67)
  - Sterling, Charles, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 68)
  - Stern, Brigitte, undated (Box 103, Folder 69)
  - Stern, Jeffrey, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 70)
  - Stern, Jerry, 1975 (Box 103, Folder 71)
  - Stern, Leonard, 1983-1990
    - Photographs (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 27)
  - Stern, Milton, 1964 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Stern, Sandy, undated (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Sternberg, Martin L.A., 1964 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Sternhell, Sam, undated (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Sterns, Marion, undated (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Stessin, Lawrence, 1957 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Stettinius, Edward R. Jr., 1938, 1940 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Stettson, DeWitt, undated (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Steven, Barry, undated (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Stevens, Beth, undated (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Stevens, Ed "Red", 1941 (Box 122, Folder 28)
  - Stevens, J.P., 1982 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Stevens, Lee, undated (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Stevens, Dr. Marvin A. "Mal", 1965
    - Photographs (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 29)
  - Stevens, Mitchell, undated (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Stevens, Morris P., undated (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Stevenson, Bryan, 2004 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Photographs (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Digital Photographs, UA_MC_319_ER_3
  - Stevenson, H.L., undated (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Stevenson, John, 1964-1967
    - Photographs (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 30)
  - Stevenson, John J., 1903, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 20)
  - Stewart, Celia, undated (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - Stewart, James, undated (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - Stewart, Potter, undated (Box 104, Folder 23)
  - Stewart, Richard, undated (Box 104, Folder 24)
  - Stickley, Linda, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 25)
  - Stickney, Phylis Yvonne, undated (Box 104, Folder 26)
  - Stiefel, Leanna, 1983-1994 (Box 104, Folder 27)
  - Stifter, Vicky, undated (Box 104, Folder 28)
  - Stile, Joseph L., 1979 (Box 104, Folder 29)
  - Still, Bayrd, 1960-1982 (Box 104, Folder 30)
  - Stillerman, undated (Box 104, Folder 31)
  - Stillman, Deanne, undated (Box 104, Folder 32)
  - Stillwell, Mary K., 1980 (Box 104, Folder 33)
  - Stimpson, Catherine, undated (Box 104, Folder 34)
  - Stimson, Henry L., 1929 (Box 104, Folder 35)
  - Stitt, Barbara, undated (Box 104, Folder 36)
  - Stoddard, Francis Hovey, 1892-1938
    - Photographs (Box 104, Folder 37)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 32)
  - Stoddard, George D., 1957-1964 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Stoddard, Richard, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Stoddard, Tom, undated (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Stohr, Ted, undated (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Stoke, Harold W., 1955 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Stoker, James J., 1958-1964 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Stokes, James, 1907 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Stoll, William, circa 1946 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Stone, George Winchester Jr., 1961-1975 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Stone, I.F., undated (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Stone, Oliver, 1988-1992
    - Photographs (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 33)
  - Stone, Ruth, undated (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Stoney, George, undated
    - Photographs (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 34)
  - Stoianovich, Dr. Traian, undated (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Stotsley, G., undated (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Stout, Gardner D., 1975 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Stout, Lynn A., undated (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Stovall, Robert H., 1977-1983 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Stover, James, 1967-1968 (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Stowe, John, undated (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Stowe, Steve, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Straetz, Ralph A., 1966, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Strand, Fleur, 1970, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Stratton, Dr. Julius A., undated (Box 105, Folder 24)
  - Straus, Mr. and Mrs. Percy, undated (Box 105, Folder 25)
  - Strauss, Lewis L., undated (Box 105, Folder 26)
  - Strauss, Roger W., undated (Box 105, Folder 27)
  - Strax, Philip, undated (Box 105, Folder 28)
  - Streich, Mrs. J, undated (Box 105, Folder 29)
  - Strine, Leo, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 30)
  - Strobel, John, undated (Box 105, Folder 31)
  - Strong, Benjamin, undated (Box 105, Folder 32)
  - Strong, David, undated (Box 105, Folder 33)
  - Strong, George Templeton, undated
    - Photographs (Box 105, Folder 34)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 31)
  - Strong, George Washington, undated (Box 105, Folder 35)
  - Strong, Kenneth, 1962 (Box 105, Folder 36)
  - Stroock, Alan M., 1984 (Box 105, Folder 37)
  - Strom, Charles, undated (Box 105, Folder 38)
  - Strom, Dr. Jordan H., 1955 (Box 105, Folder 39)
  - Strossen, Nadine, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 40)
  - Strulovici, Ely, undated (Box 105, Folder 41)
  - Strumpf, Manny M., undated (Box 105, Folder 42)
  - Stuart, William, undated (Box 105, Folder 43)
  - Studdiford, Dr. William B., undated (Box 105, Folder 44)
  - Studenski, Paul, 1912, 1956, 1958 (Box 105, Folder 45)
  - Strum, Brian, undated (Box 122, Folder 35)
  - Stumpf, Juliet, undated (Box 105, Folder 46)
  - Stumpf, Stephen, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 47)
  - Stunkard, Horace W., 1917-1954 (Box 105, Folder 48)
  - Stursberg, Amy, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 49)
  - Styne, Jule, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 50)
  - Subin, Harry, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 51)
  - Subotnick, Morton, undated (Box 105, Folder 52)
  - Subrahmanyan, Marti, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 53)
  - The Sugar Hill Gang, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 54)
  - Suhrie, Dr. Ambrose L., 1935 (Box 105, Folder 55)
  - Sullivan, Edward, undated (Box 122, Folder 36)
  - Sullivan, Fred, 1967 (Box 105, Folder 56)
  - Sullivan, John F., undated (Box 105, Folder 57)
  - Sullivan, John J., 1953 (Box 105, Folder 58)
  - Sullivan, Mary, undated (Box 122, Folder 37)
  - Sullwan, Michael, undated (Box 105, Folder 59)
  - Sun, Grace, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 60)
  - Sunderlind, Richard, undated (Box 105, Folder 61)
  - Sundheim, Dr. Benson, 1958 (Box 105, Folder 62)
  - Super, Dr. Stuart, undated (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Suriano, Silvio, undated (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Sussman, Alan, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Susuki, Nadoka, undated (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Sulton, Constance, undated (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Sverson, Arthur L., 1957 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Svigals, Philip, 1964, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Swadon, Philip E., undated (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Swanborn, undated (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Swanson, Dorothy, undated (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Swarthout, Dr. John M., circa 1958 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Swart, Dr. Michael, undated (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Sweeney, George, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Sweeney, Jan, undated (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Sweeney, Joseph M., 1965 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Sweeney, Thomas J., 1988 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Sweet, Barry E., 1987 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - Swenson, Rinehart J., undated (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Swift, Richard N., 1961, 1964 (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Swift, Robert A., undated (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - Swisher, Carl B., 1957 (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Swoboda, Ron, undated (Box 106, Folder 22)
  - Sylla, Richard, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - Symonds, B., undated (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - Syms, Parker, undated (Box 106, Folder 25)
  - Szasz, Thomas, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 26)
- T
  - Tabutesu, Sybil, undated (Box 122, Folder 38)
  - Taggart, Joseph, 1957, 1962, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 27)
  - Tagliabue, Paul, undated (Box 106, Folder 28)
  - Takei, George, undated (Box 106, Folder 29)
  - Talauco, Kathryn, undated (Box 106, Folder 30)
  - Talleton, undated (Box 106, Folder 31)
  - Tallmadge, James, undated (Box 106, Folder 32)
  - Tam, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 33)
  - Tamir, Arie, undated (Box 122, Folder 39)
  - Tanaka, Izumi, undated (Box 106, Folder 34)
  - Tanaskovic, Mary, undated (Box 122, Folder 41)
  - Tanassy, Emil George, undated (Box 106, Folder 35)
  - Tancer, M. Leon, 1970, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 36)
  - Tanchester, Dr. David, undated (Box 106, Folder 37)
  - Tanenbaum, Aaron, undated (Box 122, Folder 42)
  - Tanenbaum, Sid, circa 1946, 1972, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 38)
  - Tang, Frank, undated (Box 106, Folder 39)
  - Tanguay, James, undated (Box 106, Folder 40)
  - Taniguchi, Yasuhei, undated (Box 106, Folder 41)
  - Tanis-Lamonde, Catherine, undated
    - Photographs (Box 106, Folder 42)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 40)
  - Tanner, Rollin H., undated (Box 106, Folder 43)
  - Tannenbaum, Arthur, undated (Box 106, Folder 44)
  - Tannenbaum, Libby, 1946 (Box 106, Folder 45)
  - Tannenbaum, William, undated (Box 106, Folder 46)
  - Tanners, Dr. Nathan, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 47)
  - Tappan, Henry P., 1929 (Box 106, Folder 48)
  - Tappan, Paul W., 1958 (Box 106, Folder 49)
  - Tardugno, Irene V., undated (Box 106, Folder 50)
  - Tasco, Frank, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 51)
  - Tate, Jack B., undated (Box 106, Folder 52)
  - Taub, Henry, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 53)
  - Tauritz, Leo L., 1953 (Box 106, Folder 54)
  - Taylor, A. Wellington, undated (Box 106, Folder 55)
  - Taylor, Deems, 1962 (Box 106, Folder 56)
  - Taylor, Edward "Ted", undated (Box 106, Folder 57)
  - Taylor, Elizabeth, undated (Box 122, Folder 43)
  - Taylor, Grant E., 1957 (Box 106, Folder 58)
  - Taylor, Howard, undated (Box 106, Folder 59)
  - Taylor, Leigh H., undated (Box 106, Folder 60)
  - Taylor, Pauline, 1964 (Box 106, Folder 61)
  - Taylor, Thomas Thompson Jr., circa 1917 (Box 106, Folder 62)
  - Taylor-Thomas, Kim, undated (Box 106, Folder 63)
  - Tebbel, John, 1954, 1965, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 64)
  - Tehhula, John, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 65)
  - Teichmann, Frederick K., 1928, 1943, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 66)
  - Telkes, Maria, undated (Box 106, Folder 67)
  - Temple, Harry, undated (Box 106, Folder 68)
  - Ten Brook, A.W., 1907 (Box 106, Folder 69)
  - Tenenbein, Aaron, undated (Box 106, Folder 70)
  - Ten Eyck, Andrew, undated (Box 106, Folder 71)
  - Tenzer, Herbert, undated (Box 106, Folder 72)
  - Ternow, undated (Box 122, Folder 44)
  - Terrill, Damon A., undated (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Terte, Robert H., undated (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Tetenbaum, Marvin, undated (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Thatcher, Thomas Day, 1944 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Thailand -- Princess of Visits NYU, 1974 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Thalen, Pat, undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Thaler, William, 1956, 1959 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Thant, U, 1964 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Thieberger, Jane, 1989-1990 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Thiongó, Ngũgĩ Wa, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Thomas, Annie, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Thomas, Carl C., 1903 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Thomas, E.W., undated (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Thomas, Franklin, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Thomas, Gerald, undated (Box 122, Folder 45)
  - Thomas, Harold, undated (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Thomas, Lowell, undated (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1929 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - Thompson, Anthony, 2005 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Thompson, Charles B., undated (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, undated (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Thompson, Dr. Douglass, 1956 (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - Thompson, Gilman W., undated (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - Thompson, Dr. Glenn S., undated (Box 107, Folder 23)
  - Thompson, Hunter, 1985 (Box 107, Folder 24)
  - Thompson, Ken, 1970 (Box 107, Folder 25)
  - Thompson, Marilyn Berry, undated (Box 107, Folder 26)
  - Thompson, Robert L., undated (Box 107, Folder 27)
  - Thomson, P.L., 1939 (Box 107, Folder 28)
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 29)
  - Thoreau, Henry David, undated (Box 107, Folder 30)
  - Thorne, Perley, 1911, 1928, 1943, 1949 (Box 107, Folder 31)
  - Thorton Sisters, undated (Box 122, Folder 46)
  - Thrasher, Frederic M., undated (Box 107, Folder 32)
  - Thronson, David, undated (Box 107, Folder 33)
  - Tichauer, Dr. Erwin R., 1969 (Box 107, Folder 34)
  - Tighe, James, undated (Box 107, Folder 35)
  - Tilden, Samuel J., 1962 (Box 107, Folder 36)
  - Tillett, William S., undated (Box 107, Folder 37)
  - Tillinghast, David, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 38)
  - Tillman, Alfred Albert, undated (Box 107, Folder 39)
  - Tilton, Reverend Dr. Edgar, undated (Box 107, Folder 40)
  - Tinchel, Fran, 1972 (Box 107, Folder 41)
  - Tinker, Heddie Tracy, undated (Box 107, Folder 42)
  - Tipper, Harry, undated (Box 107, Folder 43)
  - Tippo, Dr. Oswald, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 44)
  - Tipton, Carol, 1974 (Box 107, Folder 45)
  - Tisch, Laurence A., 1969-1994
    - Photographs (Box 107, Folder 46-47)
    - Negatives (Box 122, Folder 47)
  - Tisch, Preston Robert, 1982-1996 (Box 108, Folder 1, Box 123, Folder 34)
  - Tischauer, Irwin, undated (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Tischman, David, 1964, 1968, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Titterton, George F., 1956 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Titus, Melle Stanleyetta, undated (Box 122, Folder 48)
  - Tiunov, Oleg, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Tjerandsen, Carl, 1957 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Tobel, Amy, undated (Box 108, Folder 7)